over time you will generate a lot of
fails one of the best way is to make
sure that you know where your fails art
is to organize them into folders as you
can see on this screen I have My
Documents folder here and I have three
folds on there Adobe videos and itq I've
created the itq folder specifically to
contain the actual files that I will
require for the itq course I've
downloaded the IPU assessment the ps/2
assessment the ss2 assessment and the
wp2 assessment which are the four
assessments that you will complete as
you work through the course ideally I
would like to create folders for each of
the individual units so as I gather
information and download files relating
to each of the various units of
presentations spreadsheets or word
processing I can then organize those
into for us so to simply create a folder
you would go to the cog icon and select
new folder and I'm going to call out wp2
and then I can move the wp to assessment
into that folder I'm going to create
another new folder and I'm going to call
that ps/2 and I will move the ps/2
assessment into that folder another new
folder which is ssj2 and move the
document into that and finally a new
folder and that will be IPU - so as you
can see I now have organized all of the
relevant units into their fullness so
when I download the files needed for
word process and I can store them all in
the relevant full presentations
spreadsheets and IP you